[
  {
    "question": "5-3+5",
    "answer": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "5-3+5",
    "answer": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "5+2",
    "answer": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "7+4",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "1+6",
    "answer": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "1+6",
    "answer": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "3*5+8*6",
    "answer": 63
  },
  {
    "question": "3-5+8",
    "answer": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "3-5",
    "answer": -2
  },
  {
    "question": "5+3",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "3+7",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "20/5",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "20/2",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "20/2+1",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "20/2+1-4",
    "answer": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "20/3",
    "answer": 6.666666666666667
  },
  {
    "question": "999/3",
    "answer": 333
  },
  {
    "question": "999/333",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "999/99",
    "answer": 10.090909090909092
  },
  {
    "question": "777777702/2",
    "answer": 388888851
  }
]